we don't need everybody we need a
handful of people to come together and
have a conversation about what they want
to create in the world and that's what
I'm looking for I'm looking for a few
co-conspirators to create the global
cooperative with five people working
together isn't going to be the global
cooperative but we can have the
conversations about what needs to be in
place to move it forward what's the
executive function what is the actual
step-by-step process break it down
together brainstorm together and the
more we're willing to do that openly and
transparently ie on camera if we're I'm
willing they're willing as well the
faster we can record other people and
the point isn't at any point that you
necessarily need to recruit other people
when the five of us get together we want
to create something that we enjoy that
we want to be a part of without worrying
about anyone else being a part of it and
then finding those people who
intrinsically want to be part of what
we've created and they come on board and
they add their ideas and their vision
which would make it even better for them
to participate what's working and what's
not working and we just can't keep
incrementally improving the system we're
creating the tools were creating and
keep adding more voices to it eventually
we're a big enough threshold
we've hit critical mass that what we
create together is so powerful and so
amazing that it draws in and the rest it
draws in we grow to 7.5 billion but we
don't start there we don't need everyone
to come together we only need a handful
please like and subscribe see you
tomorrow